So we've been talking a lot about specific products or people that are using SageMaker.
我们一直讨论的是特定的产品或人员在使用 SageMaker
I was wondering that if you see some group of
我想知道 你认为有一群人
people that maybe has some hesitance or hasn't been using these tools,
在使用这些工具时有些犹豫或者还没有上手使用
that you think could really stand to benefit from using SageMaker?
而你认为他们使用 SageMaker 会有很多优势吗？
The quick answer is no.
直接答案是否定的
Like what I've seen so far is that SageMaker has a use case for everyone, right?
我一直都看到 SageMaker 适合所有人使用
So we do work with companies from startups to very large enterprises.
我们与初创企业和大型公司都有合作
It was built by design.
我们从设计上就考虑了各种情形
Startups for example, are very agile,
例如 初创企业很灵活
they are very fast, they want to build products really rapidly.
他们发展很快 希望非常快速地构建产品
So they don't care too much about or they do care,
所以他们不太关心有些方面
but they don't worry too much about things like end-to-end encryption or security,
当然也关心 但是不用太担心 例如端到端加密和安全性
and all these sort of regulations that can come around a platform of service.
以及服务平台可能会出现的各种法规问题
So we do see startups
我们看到初创企业
accelerating the process through which we're building and Training Machine,
通过 SageMaker 快速构建和训练
Learning Models in SageMaker.
机器学习模型
But we also work with large enterprises that are heavily regulated.
但是我们也与受到各种法规约束的大型企业合作
We work with people in financial services.
我们与金融服务公司合作
You know, the platform needs to be PCI DSS compliant.
平台需要符合 PCI DSS 规定
We work with people in health care where the platform needs to be HIPAA compliant.
我们与医疗保健公司合作 平台需要符合 HIPAA 规定
We worked with GDPR out there nowadays.
我们如今会考虑 GDPR 条例
So SageMaker, we really put a lot of energy into making sure that
我们投入大量精力 确保 SageMaker 平台足够灵活
the platform is flexible enough to fit the needs of everyone in the ecosystem.
能够满足生态系统中所有人的需求
Now the platform is ISO, PCI, GDPR,
现在平台遵守 ISO PCI GDPR
HIPAA and all of these huge compliance capabilities
HIPAA 以及各种其他法规
are injected into the product which makes people that are heavily regulated comfortable.
使受多项法规约束的企业也能无忧地使用 SageMaker
But it's also like very flexible,
并且 SageMaker 非常灵活
a lot of examples, a lot of APIs,
有很多示例和 API
a lot of automation and which also makes
还有很多自动化工具
entry-level learners or startups to just like jump on it and then accelerate.
使初学者和初创企业能够立即上手使用 然后加速开发
Now I would really encourage all sorts of learners
强烈建议所有的学员
like students for example with
例如机器学习纳米学位的学员
a Machine Learning NANO degree or Deep Learning NANO degree at Udacity,
或者深度学习纳米学位的学员使用 SageMaker
AWS provides AWS editing credits, right?
AWS 可以提供 AWS 编辑积分
So if you think about just jumping on the program and then getting
学员可以立即使用该平台
access to some credits in this jumping on SageMaker and playing not playing with a toy,
利用积分尝试一些工具
it's the same Jupyter notebook that you have in your laptop.
Jupyter notebook 与笔记本上的 notebook 一样
But then you get a possibility to use GPUs there
但是还可以使用 GPU
and solve some deeper computer vision problems.
并解决一些深度计算机视觉问题
So I don't really see a friction in the type of people that could use a platform.
所以我并不认为 SageMaker 仅适合某一类人群
I've seen a lot of excitement from virtually people,
我发现世界上的几乎所有人
everyone around the world
都很喜欢使用 SageMaker
Yeah. It's something where with the availability of
是的能够使用 GPU
GPUs and the availability of being able to label your own datasets,
并且标记自己的数据集
it's just really powering the research and the advancement.
这些功能对研究和发展有很大的推动
So I think these things are very tied.
我认为这些功能很重要
Exactly.
没错
Yeah.
是的